Hello!
I'm a Senior Intern Lee Man Sik.
(MBC's new miniseries "Kkondae Intern" on Wednesdays and Thursdays)
"Kkondae Intern" is MBC's new ambitious miniseries...
on Wednesdays and Thursdays.
A bunch of losers came at once.
The genre of this drama is comedy, based in an office setting.
It's a so-called office comedy.
It is a favorite subject in movies and dramas.
You must be aware of the changing trends...
and lead that trend in the industry.
With changing times, office dramas have also evolved.
15 years ago, there was an office drama called "Super Rookie".
The title basically gave it away.
(Kang Ho)
At least in this drama, he starts off working full time.
Many young people are having a hard time finding jobs.
You must have struggled a lot. You look slightly mature.
In order to become an employee now, you must start as a contract worker.
Who are they?
They're the recently hired contract workers.
You work double the full-time workers,
but get treated worse than a dog. It's truly not fair.
Tell your boss.
Jo Jang Poong is here.
Labor inspector at the Ministry of Employment and Labor is the lead.
He tries to punish corrupt business owners,
but even he couldn't get around this.
I made myself clear. Don't do it.
His senior at work never approves anything.
On top of that...
I've been a public servant for 30 years.
20 years of that was in the Ministry of Labor.
I have three times more experience than you.
You saw that coming. He's talking about the old days.
- So? - When the time is right.
When's that?
At the right time, this relatable office drama is here.
It's an unbelievable situation where a senior who harassed me...
becomes my junior at work.
People can be wrong...
or have different opinions,
but they don't allow it.
They think people whose opinions are different from them are wrong.
I would call them old farts or "kkondae".
"Kkondae" could be somebody who's older...
and has a senior position at work. Superiors or bosses.
But it's not exclusive to them.
There are young people too.
If you're in a situation or a position...
to act like an old fart, you do.
This is a gratifying and touching revenge story...
surrounding their switched roles.
You're here as an intern, not a general director. An intern!
Not all interns are the same.
You must be wondering, so let's look into the main characters.
(Ga Yeol Chan)
He turns from a gentle boss to a kkondae.
He's a manager in marketing at Joonsoo Food...
and maker of Spicy Chicken Ramyeon. It's General Manager Ga Yeol Chan.
Hello, I play Ga Yeol Chan on "Kkondae Intern".
I'm Park Hae Jin.
He's handsome, tall, and fits perfectly in a suit.
Male employees are envious of him, and female employees cheer for him.
His abilities are widely recognized.
The recipient is General Manager Ga Yeol Chan.
My focus is not on increasing exports.
Through our Spicy Chicken brand,
we'll lead the way for the K-Food wave.
He invents Spicy Chicken Ramyeon which gains huge popularity,
and this self-made man gets promoted to a general manager in no time.
Team lunches are a new trend.
When I heard...
"Team dinners are an extension of work," I thought this.
When I become a boss,
I will have team gatherings during work.
He's an open-minded boss who has team gatherings during work hours.
Furthermore...
It's 6pm already.
What are you doing? Aren't you going home?
Oh, right.
He's a work-and-life balance angel who lets people go home on time.
My employees will enjoy their evenings today as well.
It's hard to tell...
whether he cares about his employees or their perception of him.
General Manager Ga,
I analyzed our products.
Did you?
He might be cursing in his head.
He underlined everything.
But he keeps his manners.
I'll look through this in detail.
No wonder.
There's no boss like him.
He's an angel. An angel.
His employees love and respect him.
He looks good.
The executives trust him as well.
However,
he may look perfect, but he has a humiliating past.
Who keeps on giving that punk work?
Don't give him work!
When he was a rookie at work, his senior wasn't fond of him,
and he looked useless.
- Hey, Yeol Chan. - Yes, sir.
There's something for you to do.
Yes, sir.
This was what he made Yeol Chan do.
You need more sticks, right?
His chubby son's homework.
This is all for you.
Your job is to reassure your senior.
What else could it be?
Besides this strange logic...
Who called that punk?
He's going to spoil the mood. Who called him?
Get rid of that!
He could have been arrested for assault with his verbal abuse.
Move that thing!
He was an evil senior who was also physically violent.
He's an intern now.
What brings you here?
His shining life becomes troubled.
I don't know if you call it a coincidence or ill-fated,
but it's a resilient relationship.
We'll be facing hardships and adversities together.
Yeol Chan must have things he wants to say...
and things he doesn't like about his employees,
but he keeps it to himself, and you can tell.
I also can't express my feelings well.
I'm similar to him in that way.
Due to his sudden honorary retirement,
he went straight back to being a senior intern.
(Lee Man Sik, the ex-general manager and the current senior intern)
Hello, I'm Kim Eung Soo,
playing the role of Lee Man Sik in "Kkondae Intern".
I'm hard at work, being a kkondae.
Let's see how kkondae he is.
How dare an intern talk? What do you know?
Before his retirement, he was always picking at his subordinates.
Seriously?
And although he retired and is now a senior intern,
his old habits are still there.
What's up with your hair?
- Excuse me? - You're here to work, not to party.
Since he keeps spitting out kkondae comments,
his coworkers have given him a new nickname,
the Kkondae Intern!
Kkon-tern?
How dare they call me that? Do they know who I am?
I got a job at the ramyeon company right out of high school,
and I worked hard at the company my whole life.
I got promoted up to Team Leader, but...
What did I do wrong?
It's not that you did anything wrong.
Then what? Because I'm old?
You know...
how they consider firing us first when we reach this age.
It's sad, being forced to retire from a company...
that I've dedicated my whole life for.
I worked hard,
for my family and for the company.
And all that there's left after all of that hard work is...
my kkondae personality.
Man Sik cannot stop here, he has a family.
He tries hard to get back into the job market, but...
I can't even evaluate it, it's too crappy.
Thanks to Yeol Chan, who is getting right back at Man Sik,
Man Sik is struggling every day.
He tries to make peace with Yeol Chan in his own way.
There is no relationship that is entirely bad.
Will Man Sik be able to sort out...
this terrible relationship?
She's a boxer who loves to eat.
She's crazy from the first day, but she loves justice.
Here's the justice warrior and an intern, Lee Tae Lee.
Nice to meet you all!
I'm Tae Lee, Lee Tae Lee!
She's a very bright and confident character.
How she comes off may leave you to think,
how did someone like her get a job at such a big company?
But she's just very unique...
and she works very hard.
I'm the queen of the copy machine.
People say that there's a way for those who try their best...
in everything they do, no matter how small the task is.
She tries to comfort herself, but the real world is a cold one.
I feel like I'm just going to end up copying forever.
Eating is her way of de-stressing.
Meet the queen of eating, Lee Tae Lee!
This is absolutely delicious.
- Boy, can you eat. - It's delicious.
Tae Lee is...
someone who's very careful with her words.
And here's her superior that just began picking on her,
seemingly having no idea of what kind of a person she is.
Can you get me lunch?
Yes, sir.
This is somewhat acceptable, but...
I'm sorry.
I suddenly really want sundae soup.
It's not just once, nor twice.
Isn't it a little too much to change the menu three times?
That's Lee Tae Lee,
just trying to get by at work.
Meet Namgung Joon Soo. He's the Joon Soo of Joonsoo Food,
and he's the rich CEO of Joonsoo Food.
We also have Joonsoo Ramyeon,
and I'm the Joonsoo in that.
Joon Soo is someone who does what he wants.
He does whatever he wants to do,
says whatever he wants to say,
eats whatever he wants to eat,
and sleeps whenever he wants to.
As you can see, in that sense,
you'd think, what kind of a lunatic is that?
He's the son of a rich conglomerate family, but also a lunatic.
I'm the only one without any shares that's from a conglomerate family.
You!
Come on.
If it's because of the tax, I have a plan.
You and I...
can get married to a Monaco woman.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Did you know?
There are people who die from eating chili peppers too spicy.
Stop it!
Are you having fun?
He pushes the chairman's buttons every time he speaks,
so obviously, he's far from being the chairman's favorite.
You!
To beat General Manager Ga Yeol Chan,
he tries to fight his battles...
Even if you're a general manager,
I can't let you have this.
If that's what you say.
The more they fight, the more we get to enjoy their beautiful faces.
He's a gentleman...
and is very sweet.
He's a really good person in real life,
and that shows through his acting.
That's why I really wanted to work with him once again.
Meet Tak Jung Eun, a five-year contract employee,
who's in love with Yeol Chan.
She wants to become a regular employee,
so she works very hard,
and she secretly loves...
General Manager Ga.
That means that everyone else...
that's not Yeol Chan is out of sight.
Mr. Lee Man Sik.
He's Mr. Lee Man Sik. How else do we address him?
She easily looks down on the old senior intern.
Nice to meet you!
And she also easily looks down on her young intern.
She's always very strict to her interns,
in fear that they may take her spot as the regular employee.
Not only does she count the times they go to the bathroom,
she even records all the coffee that they take.
Her hobby is definitely creepy to say the least.
When someone does well,
she gets scared and observes from afar.
She even writes things down.
I think that's the side of her that really resembles myself.
I understand why I've been casted this role.
My motto is to be a grown-up, not a kkondae.
The bloody survival begins now.
People really don't change.
Yes.
How can people change easily?
Will the kkondae and youngsters...
be able to grow up and learn to understand each other?
Where are your manners to your superior?
Yes, sir.
(Kkondae Intern Resume Review)
General Manager Ga, please show us.
Meet Park Hae Jin. Just him being in sight is...
an employee benefit in itself.
You know nothing, how dare you even say anything?
Meet Kim Eung Soo the stereotypical kkondae.
Nice to meet you!
Tae Lee, I'm Lee Tae Lee.
Meet Han Ji Eun. Watch out, we don't know what she'll do next.
Why is there nothing bad about him?
Meet Park Ki Woong, the definition of a good man.
Mr. Lee Man Sik.
Please bring four cups of coffee to the conference room.
And last but not least, Park Ah In,
whose boldness leaves even the kkondae speechless.
Do you know me?
What we want to know about is their past.
What did you just say?
We can't hold in our curiosity.
Let's go and take a good look at their resume.
(Let's look into their past through their resume.)
We've looked into everyone's resume,
and one person stood out in particular.
That's me.
That's Hae Jin, playing the role...
of Ga Yeol Chan, the true example of a superior in a company.
When I become a boss,
I will have team gatherings during work.
He's a perfect man, more perfect than perfection.
Tell me, where can anyone find a boss like me?
Of all of this,
the most perfect thing about him is his face.
You're so handsome!
Even this perfect-looking man has...
an issue of his own.
- I hear that you looked old... - Yes.
all throughout until middle school.
Yes, my face now is exactly how it was back then.
I've finally reached the age where my face makes sense.
I look forward to being considered to look young in the future.
Who cares if you look too old or too young?
You're handsome, anyway.
The first role that he ever took on...
was Yeon Ha Nam, a younger man in love.
He let himself known to people with his role as Ha Nam.
You're like a new person now.
And his face became more and more known.
Talks about his handsome face even reached China.
Not only that...
You're way too tall for me.
He's 188cm tall,
meaning that he can make anywhere a runway.
Just about anything he wears...
miraculously transforms into a work of art.
He has great chemistry...
with anyone beside him.
He even has great chemistry with Yang Se Hyeong.
Why are you doing this to me?
He made quite an impression in every work he was in.
In particular, he really let himself become well-known...
as Yoo Jeong.
Seol!
Let's eat lunch together.
Would you like to eat with me?
He's the best senior of all seniors,
a handsome senior who buys food for his juniors.
He surely stole everyone's hearts with that one.
He really shined as Yoo Jeong,
whose name is as beautiful as he is.
Mom, rise and shine.
Wake up.
He even got to act as a husband as sweet as Choi Soo Jong,
making everyone wish that they were married to him.
What's surprising is...
that he's not just sweet in dramas.
- You're known for your good deeds. - Good deeds?
Hae Jin is even sweet in real life.
Hae Jin is bringing such positive influence everywhere.
Since 2011, you have donated...
a total of 1.7 million dollars.
He never hesitates to donate.
He even participated in the thumbs-up challenge recently.
If any acts of kindness are needed,
you can count on him to be there.
But it's too early to be amazed.
3,000K is a good level for a background light.
- What's 3,000K? - 3,000K?
Is that the name of a new rapper?
It stands for Kelvin,
which is a measurement of the temperature of the color.
3,000K is enough to feel warmth in the room.
His face is handsome, his heart is good,
and even his brain is smart.
Who is he?
He's truly the man who has it all, who doesn't lack in anything.
I take a ruler around with me.
Look at him show off his favorite accessory.
I'm an analog person.
- What's that? - I take a ruler around with me.
What kind of a ruler is that?
He's truly extraordinary.
Even his accessories are interesting.
Do you take that ruler around with you everywhere?
- It's in my bag. - You have it in your bag?
Why do you do that?
I have a habit of wanting to measure everything.
I see.
And what he wanted to measure...
happened to be Yang Se Hyeong's height.
The more you get to know him,
the more you will like this perfect man.
Everything will be fine from now on.
We can't wait to see how perfectly he will pull off...
his character in "Kkondae Intern".
Listen to the elderly, you brat.
He's a typical Korean kkondae type.
What kind of punk comes to work later than his superior?
He's the type of person you want to avoid the most.
Kim Eung Soo portrayed a typical kkondae very well.
But there's a two-syllable word...
that Eung Soo has always hated.
I don't want to be a kkondae.
Eung Soo insists that he hates kkondaes.
Does he really?
We got very curious.
So we looked into his past.
I couldn't see you the whole day. What do you think you're doing?
There's one strong evidence that supports that he's a born kkondae.
It's his voice.
Are you kidding me?
His specialty is speaking like a kkondae.
Everyone can make a mistake when they throw a ball.
How could you not dodge it and get that on your eye? You idiot.
The characters he has played also support the theory.
He's played only characters like a traitor and gangster.
Corrupted prosecutor at best.
Do you think I haven't been a gangster?
Whether he's alive or not...
He's an all-time axis of evil who likes to harass others.
There had been numerous victims.
How dare you!
And sadly, most of them were pretty boys.
Even when he sees the heartbreaking sight of...
pretty boys bleeding and falling, he says,
What kind of a man has anemia? Shame on you.
He plays horrible villains with evil tongues.
Still, one of the characters he played was much beloved.
I'll take it and double it.
Kwak Cheol Yong of "Tazza" has become popular belatedly.
Sir, I think there will be heavy traffic on Olympic-daero.
Did Mapo Bridge collapse, you moron?
One morning,
it was the world of Iron Dragon.
He translated the name, Cheol Yong, to a more international name...
with a middle-aged man's sense of humor.
- Cheol Yong. - I didn't get that joke.
If you're asked to star in the fourth movie of "Tazza"...
I won't do it.
Against our expectations, his answer was a flat no.
(What's the reason?)
No sequels are better than the original one.
And above all, my character, Kwak Cheol Yong, is dead.
He got cranky because they mentioned the dead character, Cheol Yong.
They can always make a twin brother.
That won't be fun.
This isn't enough to say that Eung Soo is a kkondae.
Is there a dance routine that was popular back then?
Jinjinbara?
Jinjinbari.
Does that mean something?
No, it doesn't. It's just an onomatopoeia.
This dance reflects my resentment.
Is he going to do some exorcism dance?
Hello, guys.
I'm Kim Eung Soo.
Jinjinbari, jinjinbari
This cute middle-aged man...
is the real Kim Eung Soo.
You got yourself free drinks with this?
He said he would never do the jinjinbari dance again.
- Jinjinbari. - That's right.
(Jinjinbari, jinjinbari)
(Oh! Oh!)
But when he's asked to do the dance, he does his best.
He's a born dancer.
When I died, I died very comfortably.
The great dancer, Kim Eung Soo, showed his talent...
in dramas as well.
At the moment of death, he showed his presence...
with the butterfly dance.
Here's what the dance implied.
It means one lets go of all his power...
only at the moment of their death.
- And... - You sound like Kim Yong Ok.
I told you we are relatives.
- "Hence!" - But...
Flustered, Eung Soo starts to say random things.
My face then was that of a sleeping baby.
Now a baby?
A very nice baby.
- You acted a baby. - Of course.
- Could you show us the baby's face? - The baby's face.
There's no expression on the face.
A sleeping baby doesn't make any facial expressions.
He looks so calm.
He doesn't look like a baby at peace,
but Kwak Cheol Yong at peace.
Somehow, all the movies and dramas I chose to shoot end up successful.
People say I'm lucky.
But I have my standards.
Of course. That's what we asked.
Let me tell you.
It's my gut feeling.
The shocking truth is revealed. His secret was his gut feeling.
I was expecting a more logical answer.
Are you laughing at me?
We can't laugh at the irreplaceable actor,
Kim Eung Soo's gut feeling though.
It's almost not too much to say...
that he's the one who raises viewer ratings.
Come on, guys! You're flattering me!
In 2020, the viewer rating raiser, Kim Eung Soo,
will turn into a kkondae.
Let's see how successful it will be this time.
Hello, I'm Lee Tae Lee.
That's right.
Lee Tae Lee, as in Italy.
She makes a shocking appearance.
- Boy, can you eat. - It's delicious.
She's a wacky new employee...
who only eats at work.
Who is she?
We are very curious to know her past.
"Miss Granny" is a romance movie where a grandma gets her youth back.
And Han Ji Eun starred in this movie.
She used to express her rock spirit with her vibrato.
Her past is pretty shocking.
What's even more shocking is...
Your name is the worst.
Ban Ji Ha.
Ban Ji Ha means basement. So how can his band see the light?
Having no idea her name would be Italy,
she quit rock and transferred to hip-hop.
This time, I put kkakdugi in ramyeon
This time, I put a chicken neck in ramyeon
This time, I put a drumstick in ramyeon
Whether it's rock or hip-hop, she can pull off anything...
with her patience.
I put pupae in ramyeon
Stop it. I hate your voice.
There's more.
To our surprise, she was on a Korean action zombie movie.
She didn't play a zombie though.
She played a well-behaved Crown Princess.
It's difficult to tell that they are the same actress.
She's a woman of thousand faces.
This time, she's turned into a cheerful intern.
Kkondaes know nothing about ombre hair.
She's a poor intern who had to say everything she had to say...
to kkondaes and ended up being in big trouble.
Lee Man Sik, you punk!
Will Lee Man Sik end up being murdered by this character?
If you want to see what happens to her, don't miss an episode.
Hey.
What's the big deal about the permanent position?
I'm the boss here.
He's born to a rich family...
and everyone envies him.
He's got everything but one thing.
If it's because of the tax, I have a plan.
You and I...
can get married to a Monaco woman.
In Monaco, there's no gift tax nor inheritance tax.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Because of his simple brain,
he fell out of favor with his father.
If you take a look at his past,
you wouldn't believe how he ended up like this.
In Andong, Park Ki Woong was...
- So he's from Andong. - a king.
With his handsome face, he's become the king of Andong.
How dare you.
He's born with a king's face.
That's why he's been playing...
crown princes or...
You don't regret that you're engaged to me, do you?
sons of millionaires who are going to take over a major corporation.
He's got not only a gorgeous face but also gorgeous language skills.
I will make history.
Good luck with carrying out your idiotic mission.
He even pulled off the North Korean dialect.
I will show the Northern rock spirit to the South!
He ambitiously shows his North Korean rock spirit.
(Do, re, mi, fa, sol, la, ti, do)
(Do, ti, la, sol, fa, mi, re, do)
There were four handsome boys in my school.
- In Andong. - Yes, but I wasn't one of them.
Really?
- You weren't 1 of the 4? - Because you were the best?
I was just known as Park Ki Woong.
Ki Woong doesn't need any epithets.
And his name is always searched with a certain word.
When he heard Ki Woong would be here,
he mentioned the millstone dance.
You do that often, don't you?
I do it every time I'm on a variety show.
It never gets edited out, does it?
Never.
Could you show us the dance?
Please do your best.
That's right.
Ki Woong is the legendary millstone man...
who took over the whole nation with his dance moves.
(2014 version of the millstone dance)
He's Andong's handsome man...
and at the same time a flippant millstone guy.
Ki Woong is finally in his element on Kkondae Intern.
I knew he would make a big problem one day.
Ki Woong is going to make a big problem this time.
Please keep an eye on him.
How should we address you?
Mr. Intern Lee Man Sik? Or Mr. Lee Man Sik?
Mr. Lee Man Sik.
She's a bold woman who can call Mr. Lee Man Sik, Mr. Lee Man Sik.
He's Mr. Lee Man Sik. How else do we address him?
She's a forthright woman whom even Hong Gil Dong would envy.
She's Park Ah In.
Mr. Lee Man Sik.
Please bring four cups of coffee to the conference room.
She teaches a lesson...
to the kkondae intern who cares a lot about hierarchy.
Let's check out Park An In's past.
Women who look like they would be great at getting refunds...
are called the refund squad.
You're making a big mistake. Do you know who I am?
Let go of me already!
A proud member of the refund squad, Park Jun Geum was challenged...
by this bold woman.
Gosh, you surprised me.
Did you send gangsters to the wedding?
Woo Jae got a surgery!
She's got a lot of nerves to yell at the scary Park Jun Geum.
Do you know what you did?
You ruined a person's life.
She even made her speechless with her charisma.
The doctor said that.
With the experience she has,
she's become the kkondae intern's mean superior.
What's wrong, Mr. Lee Man Sik?
Do you have problems with making coffee?
She deals with the worst kkondae by being a kkondae herself.
What's the matter?
What are you doing with the package? It's gross.
Throw that away and make a new one.
They have a neck-and-neck kkondae competition.
What did you write there?
She even swears elegantly using only consonants.
She and the kkondae intern make us wonder who the winner will be.
Can I be honest?
Honestly, from Donating Angel to Iron Dragon,
no cast in the past has been better than this.
Kkondae Intern actors worked until their noses bled.
If you are curious about the unpredictable plot,
make sure you tune in.
Go for it!
(Kkondae Intern: Behind the Scenes)
(First script reading of Kkondae Intern)
In February, when winter was coming to an end,
the first script reading for "Kkondae Intern" took place.
Park Hae Jin, who plays Ga Yeol Chan,
takes out his laptop as soon as he arrives.
Han Ji Eun, who plays Intern Lee Tae Lee,
changed her hairstyle to suit her character.
She's not used to it yet.
Don't I look like a punk?
Can she go to work like this?
I know.
It's a liberal company.
The kkondae intern of a liberal company,
Kim Eung Soo is here as well.
It's an office drama, so according to positions in a company,
there are both experienced and young actors.
The age groups of the actors are diverse.
I'll try my best.
(Kim Eung Soo, playing Lee Man Sik)
I'm Park Hae Jin, playing Ga Yeol Chan. I'll try my best.
Hello, I'm Han Ji Eun, playing Lee Tae Lee.
I look forward to working with you. Let's do this!
I'm going to rely on the actors a lot.
We'll be fine as long as I do well.
Is this really their first time meeting?
The actors are passionate about their roles already.
What do you like?
You need me!
It has to be me!
Are you sure that you can work for me?
What's wrong with that?
You can try persisting.
The worst kkondae senior is working under me now?
Their roles have switched. It's a satisfying office comedy.
Hae Jin and Eung Soo show perfect chemistry.
They also take strict preventative measures...
against COVID-19.
You can get a peek before "Kkondae Intern" airs.
This is the behind-the-scenes.
It's all-exclusive.
(Guide Book of Kkondae Intern, When I Was Young)
When he was a rookie, he permed his hair,
but he wears well-fitted suits with fancy ties now.
Is this the runway?
Hae Jin shows off his model walk.
Okay!
I tried to stick to the script.
This is not a spoiler,
but I made Hotdaki.
That's what I tell myself.
He made it with his heart and soul.
It's mascot Hotdaki.
It's a strange mix of ramyeon and chicken.
When it was first revealed, people showed interest.
Meanwhile, Hae Jin and Hotdaki practice a scene together.
- We can do this. - Yes?
- Right. Left. - Right. Left.
Hotdaki's has to block General Manager Ga.
It's an important job. Can he do it?
Filming finally starts.
You have to come.
He didn't have the right timing, so it's a blooper.
Hotdaki, can you do it this time?
Oh, dear.
It's a blooper again, but Hae Jin finds him cute.
Chicken!
Hotdaki appears at the right time.
He tries his best.
It's good this time.
There are partners with chemistry...
as good as Hae Jin and Hotdaki.
- Cue! - Hae Jin and Eung Soo met...
for the first time on "Kkondae Intern".
Cue.
Hae Jin has challenged himself by acting in multiple genres,
and he showed delicate emotions.
You young brats!
"I'll take double!"
Eung Soo has gained popularity from an old movie.
The cast themselves caught people's attention.
(Spitting)
- Again. - You didn't even look.
Do I have to look?
Again. Again. Again.
Never mind.
Don't do anything.
They're cold to each other in the drama.
Why are you doing this to me?
Cut, okay.
On set, they look at each other with affection in their eyes.
We have an unexpected bromance.
When he waves,
he gives a thumbs up.
Their characters are opposite extremes of each other,
but they're both sweet.
They have a fist fight in this scene,
but they take care of each other...
so that nobody gets hurt.
They made everybody laugh on set with their irresistible chemistry.
It's great.
He sometimes does things that are unexpected.
I didn't know what to do in the beginning.
What did he do that got Hae Jin flustered?
What is he looking for?
He found massage balls, and he's very satisfied.
He uses a massage stick and improvises this time.
(It's stuck.)
Again.
- It didn't work. - It went in.
Eung Soo's ad-lib was so natural.
Hae Jin is used to him now.
That went in well.
He's being a great kkondae.
I'm surprised all the time.
Hae Jin is a kkondae.
Maybe...
he's been a kkondae throughout his life.
I'm suspicious. That's how good he is.
That's not the only thing Hae Jin is good at.
In the drama, Intern Lee Man Sik...
has to expertly open the beer bottles.
It's not easy at first,
so General Manager Ga or Hae Jin steps up to the plate.
Face this way and flick up.
Like this?
He has an odd talent.
- I can do it. Should I try? - Sure.
However, it's not as easy as it looks.
Here's a fill-in for bottle opening...
you'll never see again in Korean dramas.
I can...
You can tell from the sound that he's an expert.
You can take over.
As a substitute for Eung Soo, he flaunts his skill.
He can use any tool to open beer bottles.
They keep cheering.
It's a tough job being a cameraman.
Lee Man Sik is a kkondae as a general manager,
but young General Manager Ga is also a kkondae.
For everybody watching "Kkondae Intern",
you'll go, "That's me."
You'll be able to relate here and there...
in this drama.
Besides Lee Man Sik played by Eung Soo,
there are two more that form an intern trio.
Lee Tae Lee is played by Han Ji Eun,
and Joo Yoon Soo is played by Ro Jong Hyun.
On their first day at work, you can see their personalities.
I look forward to working with you!
Tae Lee, Tae Lee, Lee Tae Lee!
Yoon Soo, Yoon Soo, Joo... Excuse me.
We made it.
- I knew it. - I don't know why we both made it.
I don't understand.
I think I'm slightly better.
In what ways?
Because I'm Lee Tae Lee.
Man Sik doesn't have a choice.
Man Sae is in elementary school. If he wants to send him to college,
he has to exert himself.
However...
These are not the employees I want.
The interns don't know what their general manager thinks.
They're simply excited on their first day.
Their work life is going to be a struggle.
Maybe she doesn't know that.
From the first day on set, Ji Eun boosts the atmosphere.
Tae Lee is a bright and cheerful character.
Can you see the resemblance with Ji Eun?
The resemblance is about half.
I think it's 50, 50.
The resemblance is the easy-going, bright side of her.
The difference is her intolerance for injustice.
You'll know when you watch the drama,
but there were times...
when she goes overboard.
She says what needs to be said.
More than anything, she's 100 percent like Tae Lee...
in that she loves to eat.
Both when the camera is on and off, she couldn't stop eating.
I can't help it. I'll gain weight because of this.
Can I have this?
Can I eat this too?
She's totally used to her character's eating habit.
I always come on set to eat.
Watching her eat stimulates your appetite.
She's adorable when she eats.
I hope you discover Ji Eun's new charm.
Let me introduce three senior employees...
who show great chemistry with General Manager Ga.
You have the ability to look into the future. I admire you.
His specialty is flattering his seniors,
and his hobby is dumping work on his juniors.
Ko Gun Han plays Oh Dong Geun.
He obviously is an annoying character,
but he is merely trying to survive at work.
Many will be able to relate to him.
Assistant Manager Oh Dong Geun talks too much.
Everything he says is nonsense.
Hong Seung Bum plays Kim Seung Jin...
who recently became a full-time employee.
He turns from a smart intern into a young kkondae.
He's a funny character that energizes everybody.
She's been a contract worker for five years.
Park Ah In plays Tak Jung Eun.
She wants to be an employee, so she has to compete.
She's really bothered by the interns.
Jung Eun is hostile toward them.
Furthermore, she has a secret crush for General Manager Ga.
You'll find her peculiarly charming.
Because of that, she's always next to him.
She keeps on glancing at him and can't hide her feelings.
- Good luck! - Jung Eun!
With his support, she gives it a try,
but she's not that good.
Then how good is Yeol Chan?
Since his character is so perfect,
maybe his bowling skill is excellent as well.
Did you practice bowling?
Bowling?
You can't...
practice overnight.
You can probably tell, but he has a great physique.
Everything about him is perfect.
Jung Eun is attracted to him as a man,
but also really looks up to him as a coworker.
And here are the four executives at the heart of the company.
It's Park Ki Woong, Kim Sun Young, Park Jong Hak, and Ko In Beom.
This one is Chairman's son,
who is rivals with Yeol Chan,
and is a man of impeccable sense in fashion.
His name is Namgoong Joon Soo.
We have to stop him, okay?
Does that sound too fake?
Ki Woong seems to be struggling...
to get used to these somewhat fake-looking clothes.
That jacket looks like it's not complete.
You're right.
Maybe you wore it inside-out.
The zipper is inside, too.
- That's hilarious. - I can't zip it up.
It's all a part of his character.
Even his outfits are not like those of a regular employee's.
He dresses as he'd like,
says whatever he wants to,
and I'm supposed to call Eung Soo...
Mr. Lee in the drama,
but I call him brother at times.
Brother!
He really does whatever he wants.
You really wouldn't find anyone like him in real life.
But there's another person with quite unique fashion...
and that's Koo Ja Sook, played by Kim Sun Young.
Isn't this more unique?
Just her outfits are enough to make her steal everyone's eyes.
Do you not know how our Chairman looks?
Put that down!
She really shows off her charisma here.
What? Ransomware?
What happened?
There's also Ahn Sang Jong, played by Jong Hak,
who's in charge of the Marketing Department.
You have to use your brains, not just money!
And then there's Go In Beom as Chairman Nam Goong Pyo.
Why are you smacking the table?
Not only did they lead the team through the filming,
but they add depth to the drama.
These middle-aged actors are truly the gem of the drama.
And we can't forget about the cameos.
They were only on screen for a few moments,
but Jung Sung Ho and Jang Sung Kyu really left quite an impression.
I love you, Tae Lee!
Lee Min Ji, who was quite a side role in "Reply 1988,"
is a cameo in the drama,
who tries to stick up for Yeol Chan,
but gets scolded by Man Sik instead.
Do you have a crush on him?
Do you think I'm crazy?
As if she saw what was coming...
May I put on an apron?
I have to duck when you throw it at me.
She's trying to prepare herself, but...
Get rid of that thing right away!
But there was no way she could avoid Man Sik's anger.
I'm terrified.
You go, too!
- Okay. - Good.
Meanwhile,
Jeong Young Ju appears as a cameo in the drama as a celebrity.
Right from the start, she put her foot down.
I'm going to be very serious.
I'm not good at being funny.
Instead of being funny, she takes a blow at Man Sik.
Aren't you curious about what happened?
Look at this cutie, getting everyone's love on the set.
She's so cute just sitting there,
but not only that, she barks when she's supposed to.
Doggie! You have to come to Mommy!
There you are.
She came out right when she was supposed to...
and even collapsed at the right timing.
Young Ju and the puppy really showed good chemistry,
as if they were really owner and dog.
Look at her.
We're so thankful that she's in the drama,
but she even sent us a greeting.
I'm taking on a very important role...
in "Kkondae Intern".
It'll be fun for you to look for me here and there...
as you watch the drama.
Please enjoy the drama.
Best of luck to "Kkondae Intern"!
The cast's great acting, heart-fluttering chemistry, and...
It's an honor to be recording a trot soundtrack for the drama...
as a trot singer.
I'm so honored and ecstatic.
(Back in my days!)
When you're tired and feeling down, Young Tak is the man you need.
I sang with all the joy in my heart,
so I hope that you will take all the positive energy from it.
And since my voice is in the drama,
I hope that it'll feel like you are...
watching the drama with me.
"Kkondae Intern" is made with all the love and dedication.
This refreshing drama on the weak taking revenge...
is waiting for you!
- Thank you! - Thank you.
("Kkondae Intern" Highlight Previews)
Young people these days...
are so useless.
Back in my days...
Kkondae is a term for those who love to say, "Back in my days."
Imagine that annoying kkondae...
Hello!
I'm Senior Intern Lee Man Sik joining your team...
from today!
That annoying kkondae is now working for me.
It's finally my time.
Here's the office life of the passionate intern...
and his superior, who gets stressed out...
because of him.
Are you sure that you can work for me?
What's wrong with that?
It's thrilling.
They never know when the line will be crossed.
What should I do?
Absolutely nothing.
(Kkondae Intern)
What kind of a man passes out from anemia?
Young people these days can't do anything right.
From head to toe,
this man is the epitome of kkondae.
- Hello. - Good morning.
Sure.
He's the legendary kkondae boss,
Lee Man Sik.
Who dares to come to work after the general manager?
And there's an unfortunate man...
who's certainly disliked by this uptight man.
I'm sorry.
It's Ga Yeol Chan the troublemaker.
And here begins Man Sik's bullying of Yeol Chan.
Would you like some coffee?
No, stop it!
How did you even get into this company?
He says something savage at least once a day.
Just don't do anything.
Again. Again!
And of course, makes Yeol Chan do everything over and over again.
You mean, the thing that the intern mentioned before?
What are you talking about?
That was my idea!
He even steals his ideas.
Ga Yeol Chan.
- Yes, sir. - I have some work for you.
He even makes Yeol Chan do...
his son's homework for him.
What are you doing? You can't even drink.
He'd be a saint if he can last through this.
In the end, this poor intern ends up resigning.
I'm going to live.
I'm going to live and show the world.
And so, he begins preparing himself for the day he can take revenge.
A few years later...
Next up is the 200,000,000 Dollar Export Award.
Congratulations to Ga Yeol Chan of Joonsoo Food.
We'll continue to lead...
the K-food trend through our Spicy Chicken brand.
Thank you.
He became a general manager at the rival company.
Congratulations to Ga Yeol Chan for being awarded...
with the 200,000,000 Dollar Export Award!
Cheers!
There are some rules...
that he makes sure to keep as a general manager.
Team lunches are a new trend.
When I become a boss,
I will have team gatherings during work.
How lucky are we?
He's the boss that everyone wants.
One day, while he was having...
the time of his life being the best boss ever...
Hello!
I'm a Senior Intern Lee Man Sik, and I am joining your team today.
How did you get here?
That kkondae boss is back.
What happened?
You can't just barge in like this.
The kkondae general manager is losing his place in the company.
The company needs me!
I'm irreplaceable!
How can you make me quit at this point?
So, he ends up unemployed.
You think I'll have nowhere else to go?
That's right, he has nowhere else to go.
Meanwhile, there's a man...
who's very dissatisfied with Yeol Chan's success.
What if the company gets passed onto Ga Yeol Chan instead?
No way.
You need to bring me something!
Joon Soo is the Chairman's son, but losing his ground to Yeol Chan.
After hours of searching through...
This is it!
He scouted Man Sik as a senior intern,
knowing that Man Sik is Ga Yeol's weak point.
- Mr. Lee Man Sik. - Yes.
And so, they meet again,
but this time, the tables have turned.
Are you really okay with working for me?
What's wrong with that? I'm completely fine.
Then you better stick through.
Sure.
Where are your manners to your superior?
Yes, sir.
If you can't avoid it, you have to enjoy it.
Don't you expect elderly respect or kindness.
Yeol Chan decides to take his revenge on Man Sik.
Mr. Ga, would you like me to bring you a coffee?
I'd like espresso doppio lungo...
as a very dry cappuccino with whipped cream on top.
I'd also like chocolate drizzle and cinnamon powder on top.
Here's my card.
General Manager Ga is really taking his sweet revenge,
but this isn't the end.
This is impressive, I can tell that you've had...
30 years of experience in the field.
He acts so kind when there are people watching, but...
It's too old-fashioned, it's not worth reading.
He's savage when there are just the two of them.
Where is your proposal, Man Sik?
What? This dried pollack soup ramyeon is mine.
He also turns a blind eye on him when his idea gets stolen.
It's cold and raining, so what do you all say...
to some hot and spicy pizza?
I know that he can't eat a meal without soup.
Yeol Chan gave up...
on being the best boss ever to take his revenge.
It would have been great if his immature revenge worked.
Is that all you have? Copying me?
You're no match for me, punk.
He doesn't get affected by any criticism.
I need you to sway General Manager Ga.
What can I do?
With CEO Namgoong on his back,
he becomes even more thick-skinned.
No relationships are completely bad.
Smiling while reminiscing the past...
with whom I thought had an ill-fated relationship.
Rather, Yeol Chan was on the verge of breaking down.
Man Sik, I'm treating the Chinese buyers today.
Join me.
Yeol Chan's revenge never stops.
Are there no interpreters?
Yeol Chan canceled them this morning.
Yeol Chan asked him to join because he doesn't know Chinese.
He wanted to humiliate him.
However.
That man.
Because of this thick-skinned and clueless intern,
their contract almost didn't work out, but maybe not.
Thanks, Man Sik.
The buyer liked Korea's drinking culture,
so he signs the contract.
How did you get pushed over by that oldie?
It taints his reputation he worked hard to build.
Is General Manager Ga out of his mind?
I know.
- That was terrible. - Terrible?
He instantly turns from an angel boss...
into a terrible one.
Stop acting up.
Because of Man Sik, his life is messed up now.
What kind of an idiot sent ramyeon to Yeonggok Borough Office?
Then one day...
I did.
- Is there a problem? - Oh, dear.
The kkondae intern makes a huge mistake...
and sends the wrong ramyeon order.
How can you work when you can't see?
It's 300 boxes, so our team is not enough.
Let's go before anything happens.
He causes trouble to all employees,
but it ultimately gets taken care of.
- Great work. - Thank you.
- Are you crying? - I'm not.
I feel like I'm a nuisance to the team.
However...
You're not a nuisance to the team. You're a stepping stone.
What does he have in mind now?
This is it.
This is the advanced way of harassing him.
Yeol Chan turns much more immature.
You called the angel terrible.
Cancel it now.
General Manager Ga is not terrible.
There's somebody else who's actually terrible.
As he planned, his reputation improves.
Right as he thought he got his perfect revenge...
against the kkondae intern...
Man Sik, are you at the office?
Yes?
I'll send you an email,
so please make 10 copies and bring them to the conference room.
Man Sik opens Yeol Chan's computer as instructed.
However...
What's this?
He opened something he shouldn't have.
Assistant Manager Oh.
Delete it, Tae Lee.
- Look. - What's this?
Thanks to him, all the computers get a virus.
I'll take responsibility and quit.
That's not taking responsibility.
You're running away.
The kkondae intern surrenders.
You're not even half as good as Onggol.
How dare you act up?
If you like Onggol that much, get lost.
I'm going to go, jerk.
Stop talking and get lost.
Right now!
They're at it again.
How many times do I have to tell you?
- Oh, dear. - My gosh!
Nobody else knows,
but the revenge battle is raging between them.
Kkon-tern? Who do you think I am?
I need a more clever maneuver.
How immature will their next revenge be?
You never change.
Are you still upset about what happened in the past?
Will the chairman notice?
Are you curious about their amusing work life?
I'm going to crush him.
I'm going to rip him apart.
This is far from done.
("Kkondae Intern" premieres on May 20.)
Again. Again. Again.
Don't do anything.
This?
Don't do anything. Get out of here!
How should I say this?
He lost the trial, but he didn't accept it.
- He said he was going to die... - Are you all right? Honey!
Why are you doing this to me?
Why the heck are you doing this to me?
Because you don't listen.
I told you to mind your own business,
but you never listen!