INDOXXI
Support dengan like & share :)
WAS IT LOVE?
ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND EVENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
YEAR 2012
HANKUK UNIVERSITY
I, Noh Ae-jeong,
have three outstanding qualities
you will only grow to love.
A, five years of delivering newspapers
prove my drive and constant diligence.
B, four years of working
as a supermarket cashier
exhibit how precise and meticulous I am.
Enjoy the movie. Hello, sir.
-C, I'm one to never give up...
-Please head left.
-...on my dreams.
-Enjoy the movie.
-Welcome.
-You can knock me down,
but I will always get up.
And that is why I, Noh Ae-jeong,
hope to join Korea's number one
film studio Ten Film...
Shinyi Media...
At Thumb Film's Accounting Department,
I will showcase my three traits
and deliver--
-I'm sorry, sir.
-We're in the middle of an interview!
Take it outside.
EPISODE 1
Seriously?
Have you not heard of silent mode?
I apologize.
Apart from part-time jobs, are you
familiar with any accounting software,
or programs like Microsoft Excel,
PowerPoint, or Word?
I used PowerPoint in university.
Right. Well, according to your resume,
you apparently dropped out of university.
That's right.
Dropped out in 2006? Hold on a second.
One, two...
How many years of study did you complete?
I dropped out
halfway through my senior year.
Wait, hold on a second.
You only had a semester left,
so why did you choose to drop out?
Was there some sort of an issue?
Ha-nee!
-Ma'am, you're here.
-Goodness.
I apologize for being late.
I couldn't get off work earlier.
It's all right.
-It's nothing, but...
-Gosh, thank you.
Ha-nee.
The truth is...
MY FAMILY, MOM
The kids must've asked
why she didn't draw her dad.
It's my fault
for not being attentive enough.
MY FAMILY, JEONG-U, DAD, MOM
DAD, SISTER, ME, MOM
Ha-nee, when your mother gets home,
why don't we light up a candle
and make a wish?
No?
But it's Christmas Eve.
You can wish Santa for something--
That's a lie.
What do you mean?
Santa doesn't exist.
Just like my dad.
Ha-nee, your dad is up in heaven--
That's a lie.
Why is that a lie?
Ha-nee,
let's just say that he died, okay?
Why?
Well,
your mom wants to think of it that way.
Why?
Well...
You see,
there are some people
you'd rather wish were dead.
You'll understand when you're older.
Why?
Well...
How about your mom and I promise
to make up for your dad?
What? My goodness.
DISCOUNT FOR NEW LOANS
Was there some sort of an issue?
-Ms. Noh?
-Sorry?
THUMB FILM EMPLOYEE RECRUITMENT
APPLICANT: NOH AE-JEONG
If you have nothing else to say...
I became a mom.
I got pregnant at 23
and had to raise my child alone.
I wasn't able to continue my studies,
but I don't regret any of it.
Caring for my daughter wasn't easy,
but it was a joy to see her grow up.
She turned six this year.
Oh, I see.
When she was young,
I could get by on part-time jobs.
But she needs to start school soon
and I want her to dress in nice clothes.
-That's why I'm looking for stability--
-Right.
I hear you loud and clear.
RESUME: NOH AE-JEONG
Gosh!
In we go.
What's wrong?
What on earth happened?
Mom, no. Stay back.
Mom?
Ha-nee, stay back. You'll hurt yourself.
Mom, keep her there.
I lost my grip and it fell.
It's all my fault.
It's not your fault.
The cheap cup is to blame.
Just a second, Ms. Noh.
Why a film studio of all places?
Other companies have
accounting departments,
but you applied for a job
at a film studio.
That's what I want to know.
It's over now.
Wait there. I'll be right over.
YEAR 2006
Because I had a dream.
DIRECTED BY OH DAE-O
PRODUCED BY NOH AE-JEONG
Before I became a mom,
my dream was to become a film producer.
That was so cool!
-Congratulations.
-It was awesome.
That was incredible.
I can be asked to push pencils
for all I care.
Working at a film studio in any capacity
would be enough.
Is that important?
That dream of yours, I mean.
I may be barely scraping by,
but that hasn't changed who I am.
I promised myself
when I first learned that I was pregnant.
My dream, my life, and my child.
I wasn't going to give up on any of them.
I know it won't be easy.
However,
I want to set an example for my child.
I want her to see me achieve my dream.
What is it? Was that from
the company you interviewed for?
Were you hired?
Grandma, what does "hired" mean?
The silence is killing me.
Answer my question.
Come on.
Mom.
I'm hired.
They hired me.
-Really?
-I got in.
-My gosh!
-Mom?
-Goodness me.
-What's "hired"?
My gosh. Sweetie pie!
My adorable little puppy.
I can't believe it, Mom.
It's too good to be true!
-Goodness.
-Mom?
What a miracle.
Have you all made a wish?
All right, then.
Let's see who blows out the candles first.
One.
Two.
Three!
-Merry Christmas!
-Merry Christmas.
Have a good day.
Gosh, it looks brand new.
DRY CLEANING
MR AND MRS DRY CLEANING
-Look. Isn't mine adorable?
-I picked that first.
-No, I did.
-Come on. We'll be late for school.
Hurry!
Either you watch that or eat.
Stop nibbling and do one or the other.
Why leave the TV on
when no one's watching it?
Unbelievable.
The key to success these days
is multitasking.
How about I multitask on you
and smack you front and back?
I'm back!
Ta-da. Fresh from the dry cleaner's.
So you can start afresh at your new school
and keep the momentum going
until you graduate.
As if I'd be able to really start afresh
in a second-hand uniform.
That's rich coming from someone
who had to transfer schools
only one month into the semester.
Also, know this.
This will be the last time
you transfer schools.
Your days of swapping schools
are now long gone.
-Fine.
-This is for you.
-What's this?
-Your personal sandbag.
Don't get into trouble on your first day
and squeeze this hard
when you want to hit someone.
If that doesn't work,
get in their faces
and threaten them with words.
You call that parenting?
Mom, that hurts.
By the way, when will your company
pay your last month's salary?
I already told you
that it'll be wired soon.
Anyway, a big investor will come by
to hear our presentation today.
Is that why
you stayed up all night working?
Who's the director?
Bong Joon-ho? Park Chan-wook?
I can't believe you know those names.
What else would I expect
from a daughter of a film producer?
Stop changing the subject.
After the last film tanked,
most employees in the company resigned.
Who would this investor
even bet his money on?
Who else?
The studio's bookkeeper of eight years
who was promoted as a producer.
Your daughter, Noh Ae-jeong.
How can a bookkeeper
become a film producer?
I may not seem like it,
but I was once a promising student
of the film industry.
My boss finally noticed my talents.
They say that the sparrow near a school
sings the primer.
You've worked there for eight years,
so let's hope you learned something too.
Right, of course.
Wait. What did you just say?
Whatever.
If you don't get paid
at the end of this month too,
you should quit your trash job.
Mom, please. That would be disloyal of me.
Besides, I have a good feeling
about this next project.
Does that mean
we won't have to pay rent anymore?
The rent?
Don't you worry
because I'll buy this darn house.
That's so cool, Mom.
Up top!
THUMB FILM
This is odd.
I can't get in touch with him.
Maybe it's our cell reception.
Maybe he got lost.
It's true that our office
is hard to locate.
He's here!
-Goodness. Welcome.
-Hello.
All right then. Hye-jin,
escort them to the conference room.
-It's this way.
-We're--
Over here.
Here we go. You've got this.
-Faster.
-Go, go!
-Nice.
-All right.
Shoot!
-Go, go!
-So young and innocent.
He's not too bad.
-Thank you.
-This is for you.
-Please take this.
-You were awesome.
That was incredible.
School starts in 90 seconds.
Hurry up, everyone.
Gosh, you stink of sweat.
Get your butts inside!
RESPECT YOUR TEACHERS
Stop right there.
Article 13 Section One
of Hanbak Middle School's rule book.
Students without name tags
will receive penalty points
for bad conduct.
Aren't you aware of that fact?
-I'm not.
-Fine.
Then I'll give you a chance.
You have 30 seconds
to clip your name tag in the right place.
-I don't have one.
-You don't?
This is my first day
at this school, you see.
Did you really think
I'd fall for that palpable lie?
Follow me inside
and find out for yourself.
What an attitude...
How dare you talk back to a teacher?
Do you want more penalty points?
I think she's telling the truth.
Get your hands off me.
A new student is joining my class today.
I'm glad I got a smart one.
Are you sure she's one of yours?
I think so.
Your name is...
Noh Ha-nee, right?
That's right.
I'll take her with me then, Mr. Jang.
-Shall we?
-Sure.
Have a good day then.
Husband over Flowers,
the new movie of Thumb Film,
follows a woman
who's been single for 14 years
as she miraculously finds love.
The award-winning Director Kim Sang-ho
will showcase his style and vision.
That combined with
the fresh love story
will hopefully draw in the audience...
The...
audience.
The cost of production
will be 6.6 billion won.
With the costs
for marketing and advertising--
We estimate ten billion won in total.
Right.
How do you expect to
raise all that money?
We hope for you, the investor,
to invest in our movie.
That's a shame. It seems like
there's some kind of misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
Thank you.
"Nine Capital"?
Wait, a money lending company?
Why are you here at our studio though?
You boss at Thumb Film
borrowed 700 million won from us.
-What? 700 million?
-700 million won?
That's right, and just so you know,
the principal and interest combined
is 1.05 billion won.
1.05 billion won? Holy shit.
Hye-jin, call the boss.
-His phone is turned off.
-What?
As you can see, Mr. Wang is unreachable.
So you, Ms. Noh, must pay back his debt.
Me?
What? Why?
Why me? Why must I pay it back?
-I--
-Because you...
stood surety for him.
What is this?
What the hell is this?
JOINT SURETY AGREEMENT
You're no longer our bookkeeper.
You're now Noh Ae-jeong the producer.
Produce a movie of your own
and make a name for yourself.
No. No, don't!
Don't sign it.
Quit paying rents and buy your own house.
NOH AE-JEONG
That's it, Producer Noh.
JOINT SURETY AGREEMENT
Hold on, sir. Wait!
My boss wouldn't have done this to me.
I only thought I was signing off
an investment of 70 million won.
How can it go from 70 million
to over a billion won?
Sir, please. Please forgive me this once.
Ms. Noh!
Sir, wait. Please!
Choi Hyang-ja, born July 5, 1960.
A body scrub master.
She's your mother, am I right?
What the hell is this?
Noh Ha-nee, born February 15, 2007.
Transferred to Hanbak Middle School
due to personal reasons.
She's your daughter, am I right?
Are you serious right now?
You have two weeks to pay back the debt.
If you aren't able to pay by then,
unpleasant things
might happen to those around you.
Don't forget that.
Ms. Noh, are you all right?
Are you sure about that?
And you?
I made
the Statue of Liberated French Fries.
Kids are pretty much the same
whichever school they go to.
Hold on. Right, got it.
Bullseye.
-Did you see that?
-Nice!
-Nice one.
-Good shot.
Sorry about that, new girl.
I bet I startled you.
What should we try next?
Mr. Wang!
Ms. Noh, isn't this breaking and entering?
Where is the bastard?
-What on earth is this?
-Where is he?
Rat bastard.
Did he really run off?
-He was already sued.
-What?
Let me see.
Gosh, it stinks.
LIFE IS DO OR DIE
Ms. Noh, isn't this a contract?
PUBLICATION RIGHT OF LOVE IS NONEXISTENT
"Love Is Nonexistent"?
Jeez, this is really old.
The terms aren't even fair.
He left behind stupid trash, that bastard!
Tell me about it.
It must've been worthless
for it to have been stuck under the pot.
You fucking bastard.
I ought to...
Fuck...
You shitty little jackass!
Please calm down.
Gosh!
Really?
Hello?
Yes. Ha-nee?
SCHOOL TRANSCRIPT
STUDENT NAME NOH HA-NEE
MOTHER NAME NOH AE-JEONG
Hello, I'm Noh Ha-nee's mother.
Where is the counseling office?
It's at the end of the hallway
on the second floor.
End of the hall, second floor?
Thank you.
Excuse me, Ms. Noh!
Ha-nee!
Ha-nee.
This is Ha-nee's mother.
Yes, I'm Ha-nee's mother.
Look.
This is what your daughter did
to my son's face.
I'm so upset.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It's my fault.
-Ma'am, I'm sorry.
-Mom.
Come here. Come here and apologize.
-Quickly.
-I don't want her apology.
I want to hold
a School Violence Committee meeting.
Sir.
A School Violence Committee
meeting can hurt all the students.
Mr. Oh.
Are you playing dumb
because it's not your student
who got the nosebleed?
Mr. Jang, that's not--
Anyway, we'll see if the meeting
will hurt the kids or not when we hold--
Ma'am, I'm sorry. I apologize.
-Please forgive--
-Let go. What are you doing?
-I'm sorry.
-I don't need to hear it anymore.
Let's have men settle this.
Where is her dad?
I don't have a dad.
I have no such thing as a dad,
so if you have something to say,
just say it to me.
-Ha-nee.
-I knew it.
There was a reason why she was
-so ill-behaved.
-Honey, stop.
Ms. Noh.
Let me give you an advice
as a fellow parent.
Children from single-parent families
should be raised more strictly.
If you pity them and indulge them,
it shows that they have no dad.
Sir.
Don't you think
what you just said is unacceptable?
She...
has a dad.
I'm her dad and her mom.
My kid has never once
been raised with only half the love.
You can charge me for the hospital bill.
I'll fully compensate your son
for the pain he suffered.
But...
how will you compensate
for my child's heartache?
I'm sorry for all the commotion, Mr. Oh.
Excuse us. Let's go.
Ms. Noh.
-Ms. Noh.
-I'll see them off.
Please don't mind them.
Mom, I really didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't hit him. He first...
Mom?
-Mom, are you listening?
-Noh Ha-nee.
Transferred to Hanbak Middle School
due to personal reasons.
Let's go. We have to go.
-What's wrong? Where are we going?
-Let's go.
Mom, let go of my arm.
Mom, do you really think it was my fault?
Be quiet, Ha-nee.
Ha-nee, let's go home and talk, okay?
Let's go home.
Ha-nee! What are you doing?
Hey.
Why won't you listen to me?
Ha-nee.
Before you say sorry,
before you apologize,
shouldn't you listen to me first?
I asked you already.
I asked you not to get into trouble
on the first day of school.
Never mind. I don't want to hear it.
How long do I have to live
with my heart in my mouth because of you?
Whose fault is that?
What?
It's your fault!
If you hadn't given birth to me,
you and I didn't have to be treated
like shit!
This is useless!
No matter what I do,
the fact that I don't have a dad
doesn't change.
That kid, Han Chan-yeong
deserves a nosebleed.
He always bullies me.
Today Ha-nee taught him a lesson.
Nobody has ever stood up for me.
Ha-nee was the only one who helped me.
Ha-nee didn't do anything wrong.
How much did that CEO bastard
scam you for?
About ten?
It's ten billion won.
What a bastard.
I realized that you shouldn't call
something the worst so recklessly.
Because that might not be the worst.
Drink up.
I'm buying this for the most
miserable person on Earth today.
Sook-hee.
Why do bad things always happen
all at once?
I'm not sure.
Since they all came at once,
they'll probably leave all at once.
No.
They won't.
Because they didn't 14 years ago.
Would it have been different
if I hadn't met him then?
If you pity them and indulge them,
it shows that they have
no dad.
Bullocks. It doesn't at all.
I look perfect.
-Mom! I'm home.
-Yes.
Here.
-What? Did you drink?
-A little.
Eat this.
Where's Ha-nee? Is she in her room?
I'm her dad
and her mom.
Sir, wait!
Stop. Please wait.
I'm sorry.
Sir!
Thank you.
I'm so tired. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-I almost missed it.
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
It's creased.
It must be something important.
Yes, I've lost days of sleep
to write this proposal.
What am I going to do?
Anyway, thank you.
Hello.
You're Ha-nee's homeroom teacher, right?
Good to see you.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. That was my mistake.
I guess you still don't recognize me.
Pardon?
Long time no see, Ae-jeong.
Ae-jeong, open the window.
Open the window?
I missed you.
Don't worry about Ha-nee.
I'll take good care of her.
Okay.
Goodbye. Go on.
Ae-jeong! See you again.
I'll call you!
Why of all people is he Ha-nee's
homeroom teacher?
This is driving me nuts!
Yes, Ha-nee.
You look happy.
What?
Well...
Here.
Thank you for trusting me yesterday.
Goodbye.
Ha-nee.
If you're having a hard time,
tell me, all right?
Thanks for this.
Okay.
Thank you.
HUSBAND OVER FLOWERS
-Excuse me.
-I'm sorry.
Hello, sir.
I'm Producer Noh Ae-jeong of Thumb Film.
I requested an investment meeting
last time.
I heard Thumb Film went bankrupt.
No, it didn't.
The company isn't in a good situation,
but we're working on something.
Once you read it, you'll see that
the script is very solid.
I heard another company
was working on this.
No, our company signed a contract
a long time ago.
No, this was sold to a different company.
Let me tell you this so you don't go to
another company and get humiliated.
There's no company that would invest
in Thumb Films in this industry.
Sir.
This is Producer Noh Ae-jeong
of Thumb Film.
Ms. Noh, are you really doing this?
Sir, I heard some strange news.
There's a ridiculous rumor going around
that you're working with another company.
People in this industry spread gossip
so recklessly, don't they?
I'm sorry, Producer Noh.
I heard Mr. Wang fled.
He breached the contract first.
-What?
-It worked out for the better.
Thumb Film didn't even have
the ability to produce my work anyway.
I'm still here.
Sign a contract with me again.
You know me.
Since I first met you,
I've been working really hard.
I'll do my best to make your work
-see the light--
-You should give up.
Please, sir.
Producer Noh.
This is your first film, right?
Let's be frank. Can you bring in the money
and hire all the actors I want
for this film?
Well...
I know you've been working really hard
for several months,
but you don't have the ability
to produce my work.
THUMB FILM
SUMMER IN LOVE
CEO of Thumb Film.
CEO WANG SEONG GYU
Ms. Noh.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
Let's sell whatever we can here.
I'll pay your salary with that money.
But you need the money more than I do.
I'm okay.
For the time being,
I decided to focus on
what to do with the bastard.
Pardon?
Just you wait.
I'll grab his neck and throw him down
on asphalt.
I'll punch his face
and beat him to a pulp
until all his teeth fall out.
Are you okay?
Goodness.
-It's bleeding.
-Goodness.
Gosh.
Throw this out.
Okay.
Goodness.
This is a really old
handwritten manuscript.
I don't care if it's handwritten or not.
Burn it all!
Okay.
But...
this was written by
the author Cheon Eok-man.
Cheon Eok-man.
-This is really old.
-He left behind stupid trash!
LOVE IS NONEXISTENT
"Love Is Nonexistent."
What?
What's this?
Hye-jin.
-A wet wipe
-A wet wipe.
A wet wipe.
Easy now.
Cheon Eok...
CHEON EOK-MAN
No way. This copyright contract...
It's signed by the best-selling author,
Cheon Eok-man!
Goodness!
-We did it! We're saved!
-Yes!
We did it!
This place is unbelievable.
He must be loaded
since he owns a loan company.
There's a grass lawn!
The house is beautiful.
It's really big.
Ms. Noh.
Yes?
Run!
Stay back!
Get back!
Go away!
I was told
that you wanted to tell me something.
Well...
Actually...
Please have a seat.
Let's go.
Well, actually...
I would like to
do business with you.
Business?
This is the copyright contract
of Writer Cheon Eok-man,
the number one author
that investors want to invest in in 2020.
If I make a movie with that,
I can attract over ten million viewers,
and repay the loan of one billion won
in a lump sum with the proceeds.
I'm not sure.
Who would invest in a film company
that was abandoned by its CEO?
There's no company that would invest
in Thumb Films in this industry.
You don't have the ability
to produce my work.
Even if you have the copyright,
who would trust you
and make an investment?
I believe we're both busy.
So you better leave.
Then
why don't you make that investment?
Ms. Noh.
I...
only invest in people I can trust.
If it's worth money,
I trust people
and invest as much as I want.
I would even risk my life.
If you give me a chance,
I'll prove that I, Noh Ae-jeong,
am capable as a producer.
Please stop.
Do you mean that you are willing
to risk your life
for this investment?
I'm confident.
Because my life
is in the hands of my family.
Fine. I'll give you an opportunity.
-An--
-An opportunity?
An opportunity?
First, I need someone
to write the scenario.
Cheon Eok-man, the original author,
should do it.
-What?
Cheon Eok-man?
And as for the actor...
ACTOR RYU JIN DEBUTS IN HOLLYWOOD?
How about Ryu Jin?
You see, I'm a fan of his.
Ryu Jin?
Are you talking about that celebrity
who'll be debuting in Hollywood?
Does it have to be him?
There are many actors in Korea.
Like I said, Ryu Jin will be the actor,
and Cheon Eok-man, the writer.
If you succeed,
not only will I settle your debt,
but I'll also invest in the movie myself.
Ten billion won.
Ten billion won?
LETTER OF INTENT
You have eight days.
If you fail to keep your promise,
you should be prepared.
Tell him never to look for me again
and that the next time I see him,
I'll have his head.
-Over here.
-Pose for the camera.
-This way.
-Please look here.
-Hello.
-This way, please.
Okay, thank you.
Please pose.
-Please look this way.
-Please strike a pose.
Okay, thank you.
-Hey, Hye-jin.
-Ms. Noh.
I've almost arrived at Mr. Cheon's house.
How's it going over there?
It doesn't look easy,
but I'll have to make it work.
You said you guys knew each other.
I'm sure he won't ignore you.
Right.
We did have a special relationship.
Please pose for the camera.
Okay, thank you.
Jin.
Well...
Let's kiss.
HELLO, DAN-BI
IN THEATRES APRIL 20
Not too long ago,
you were invited to Hollywood
and came back to Korea this morning.
Have you brought back some good news?
I'm just doing my best at all times.
Did you meet with Director James Caramel?
He's a big fan of Korean cuisine.
Does this mean
you're set to debut in Hollywood?
I think around next week, I'll be with
James under the Californian sun
with a glass of mojito in my hand.
Who's the co-star?
No comments on that.
Since many people
have been waiting for me,
I'll make sure to hold
a press conference soon.
I look forward to today's movie,
and I hope many of you will check it out.
Thank you.
Jin!
Jin, don't go to Hollywood. Stay with me.
Wait!
-Wait a minute!
-Jin!
-Move aside! No photos!
Jin! Hold on!
RYU JIN'S DIEHARD FAN BARGES IN
DURING A MOVIE PREVIEW
So you couldn't meet him?
I'm going to try again.
I'm going to visit his agency
or even his house.
Good. You said you guys had
a special relationship.
You will find another opportunity.
Special?
Yes.
We were almost special.
-Noh Ae-jeong!
-No.
-Just drink it!
You said you would!
No. Just give me the penalty.
-Writing her name with her butt!
-No!
Seeing how much alcohol is left,
she should kiss someone to make up for it.
You're right!
No way!
-Lucky you.
-Come on.
-With whom?
-Me, of course.
No, not you.
I...
will pick
whom to kiss!
-What?
-Come on.
Here I go.
-All right, let's go.
-Ae-jeong.
-Let's go.
-Let's hurry.
-Wait up!
-Hey!
-Wait!
I'm curious to find out.
Wait for me!
Open up!
Let's go.
-Hurry up.
-Hey!
-What?
-Look at her!
Jin.
Well...
You see...
So...
Let's kiss.
No!
What is that?
That's disgusting!
Ae-jeong, what about we go somewhere else?
My shoes.
My shoes!
My shoes...
Hey!
What?
We're no match for Hollywood.
Don't be ridiculous.
We have the almighty Cheon Eok-man.
I'm not sure about that.
I can't seem to reach him.
What? You can't reach him?
Jin!
Jin! I got some ointment. Let me see.
Oh, come on. I'm fine.
Not at all.
She should've collapsed
on top of me instead.
What if the wound scars?
Hey.
I'm really fine.
Rather, I'm happy.
I witnessed a fan who loved me so much
that she'd pounce on me.
Jin.
Oftentimes, I'm so proud
to be your manager. No.
I'm so proud to be your close friend.
It doesn't matter how much
this world changes.
Once a brother, always a brother.
Got that?
Jin!
How on earth did a fan
barge at him like that?
How could you let Jin fall down?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Ms. Song.
I'm sorry I got worked up.
I was worried that you were badly injured.
Anyway, good work on the audition
and the film preview.
While we wait for James Caramel
to call back,
how about we have a party
to celebrate your return?
-I've reserved a place.
-You can have the party without me.
I have a previous engagement.
With whom?
No one told me about this.
With Kwae-nam.
Let's go grab a drink,
Kwae-nam.
Okay.
I should take the ointment.
Jin.
THIS IS NOH AE-JEONG FROM THUMB FILM
HELLO, MR. CHEON EOK-MAN
I AM WRITING TO YOU BECAUSE
WE WOULD LIKE TO MAKE A MOVIE
WITH A SCRIPT YOU WROTE
SINCERELY, NOH AE-JEONG FROM THUMB FILM
Please.
I beg you, Mr. Cheon.
Please take a look at my email.
My future is in your hands.
Please.
To all the gods out there,
please help me out this once. Please.
YOUR MAIL HAS BEEN SENT
ANNUAL SPRING LITERARY CONTEST
How great is he
that everyone loves him so much?
Let's take a look.
"Love Is Nonexistent."
SHE VANISHED. SHE LEFT ME OUT OF THE BLUE
"When it was announced that
the wish of the winner will be granted,
I swung the sword with all my might
with the thought that I could finally
tell her how I felt."
"As I held her hand for the first time
and as our eyes met,
I felt as if I was drifting away."
Do not hold the sword in your left hand.
Your left hand is close to your heart,
so it will only endanger you
when you wield the sword.
So that was why.
That was why
my sword swayed in front of you.
"Even until then, I had no idea
that the woman I loved wanted to kill me."
No way.
Does that mean she betrayed him?
It's a historical piece,
and it's also melodramatic
and action-packed.
This really is something.
THIS IS CHEON EOK-MAN.
IF YOU'RE FREE, I'D LIKE TO MEET YOU
AT MARAGON CITY HOTEL'S COFFEE SHOP
AT 1 P.M. TODAY.
He replied.
Mom!
-Mom!
-My goodness, what's wrong?
Mom, Cheon Eok-man replied back.
He replied!
Cheon Eok-man!
Grandma, what's wrong with her?
-I have no idea.
-Cheon Eok-man!
Who is Cheon Eok-man?
Cheon Eok-man!
He wanted to see me immediately.
He wrote it before he became famous,
so it's special to him.
No way! I think we've hit the jackpot!
Calm down and be patient.
I'm going to persuade him no matter what.
-Okay!
-Bye.
Hello?
Yes, I'm on the 26th floor.
Yes.
Okay.
WRITER CHEON EOK-MAN
Is this Producer Noh Ae-jeong?
What?
Hello?
A DIEHARD FAN BARGES IN
THINKING OF YOU WAS WHAT I DID ALL MY LIFE
TO AE-JEONG
Hello.
I'm Cheon Eok-man.
WAS IT LOVE?
You used to know the writer Cheon Eok-man?
How does it feel to meet me again
in 14 years?
Why do I need that sick bastard's help?
So you've failed your mission.
No!
You've changed a lot.
How could I forget you, Ae-jeong?
I waited and waited for her back then.
I've missed you a lot.
Will the sun ever shine
for someone like me?
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs